From the World of Peter Pan.
Tinker Bell and the Pirate Fairy is a animation,
family film directed by Peggy Holmes.
Zarina, a smart and ambitious dust-keeper fairy who’s captivated by Blue Pixie Dust and its endless possibilities, flees
Pixie Hollow and joins forces with the scheming pirates of Skull Rock, who make her captain of their ship.
Tinker Bell and her friends must embark on an epic adventure to find Zarina, and together they go sword-to-sword
with the band of pirates led by a cabin boy named James, who’ll soon be known as Captain Hook himself.
Tinker Bell (voice), played by Mae Whitman.
Zarina (voice), played by Christina Hendricks.
James (voice), played by Tom Hiddleston.
Silvermist (voice), played by Lucy Liu.
Iridessa (voice), played by Raven-Symoné.
Rosetta (voice), played by Megan Hilty.
The Pirate Fairy (originally titled as Tinker Bell and the Quest for the Queen or alternatively Tinker Bell
and the Pirate Fairy) is a 2014 American animated fantasy film directed by Peggy Holmes.
It is the fifth direct-to-video feature-length animated film in the Disneytoon Studios' Tinker Bell
film series and the Disney Fairies franchise, based on the character Tinker Bell from J.
Barrie's Peter Pan.
The film features the voices of Mae Whitman, reprising her role of Tinker Bell, Christina Hendricks as
a dust-keeper fairy named Zarina, and Tom Hiddleston as James (a young Captain Hook).
The film explores themes of fairy tale, fairy,
pirate, curiosity, duringcreditsstinger.